Guide to the Albert Hazen Wright Papers, 1820-1960
Hazen Wright, Albert Papers, 1820-1960
- Series XIII: Photographs, Photo Albums, and Scrapbooks
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Floyd's Island Prairie, 1921-22 (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - Okefenokee Swamp, 1921 (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - Okefenokee Swamp, 1921 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Billy's Island, Bay and Lake, 1921-22 (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - Okefenokee Swamp, 1921-22 (Box 37, Folder 52)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Specimen found on Billy's Island (Box 37, Folder 53)
  - Okefenokee Swamp, 1921-22 (Box 37, Folder 54)
  - Okefenokee Swamp-Specimen, 1921-22 (Box 37, Folder 55)
  - Okefenokee Swamp, 1922 (Box 37, Folder 56)
  - Okefenokee Swamp, 1921-22 (Box 37, Folder 57)
  - Okefenokee Swamp, 1913 (Box 37, Folder 58)
  - OkefenokeeSwamp-Chesser's Island; Frances Harper Photographs, 1913 (Box 37, Folder 59)
  - OkefenokeeSwamp-J.C.Bradley Photographs, 1913 (Box 37, Folder 60)
  - OkefenokeeSwamp-J.C.Bradley Photographs, 1913 (Box 37, Folder 61)
  - OkefenokeeSwamp-J.C.Bradley Photographs, 1913 (Box 37, Folder 62)
  - OkefenokeeSwamp-FrancesHarper Photographs, 1912 (Box 37, Folder 63)
  - Okefenokee Swamp, 1912 (Box 37, Folder 64)
  - Okefenokee Swamp, 1912 (Box 37, Folder 65)
  - OkefenokeeSwamp-FrancesHarper Photographs, 1912 (Box 37, Folder 66)
  - Group at Laurelwood; Prof. Alkenson's Place at Cornell Heights (Box 37, Folder 67)
  - Letter of L. Agassiz to B.G. Wilder, Oct. 29, 1875 (Box 37, Folder 68)
  - First Faculty of N.Y.S. Veterinary College (Box 37, Folder 69)
  - Enfield Glen between 1896 and 1899 (Box 37, Folder 70)
  - International Botanical Congress (Box 37, Folder 71)
  - A.H. Wright and Family (Box 37, Folder 72)
  - Cornell University (Box 37, Folder 73)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 74)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 75)
  - Miscellaneous, 1927 (Box 37, Folder 76)
  - Plant specimen, 1927 (Box 37, Folder 77)
  - Miscellaneous, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 78)
  - Miscellaneous, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 79)
  - Miscellaneous, 1917-22 (Box 37, Folder 80)
  - Fish negatives, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 81)
  - Fish negatives, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 82)
  - Fish from Danby and Wilseyville Creek, 1928 (Box 37, Folder 83)
  - Irises, 1927 (Box 37, Folder 84)
  - Irises, 1927 (Box 37, Folder 85)
  - Irises, 1926-35 (Box 37, Folder 86)
  - Specimen, 1930 (Box 37, Folder 87)
  - Specimen found in Ithaca, NY, 1928 (Box 37, Folder 88)
  - Irises, 1928 (Box 37, Folder 89)
  - Irises, 1927-28 (Box 37, Folder 90)
  - Iris Notebook (Box 37)
  - Irises, 1927-31 (Box 37, Folder 91)
  - Iris Society, 1927 (Box 37, Folder 92)
  - Irises (Box 37, Folder 93)
  - Irises, 1927-28 (Box 37, Folder 94)
  - West Virginia, 1931 (Box 37, Folder 95)
  - West Virginia, 1931 (Box 37, Folder 96)
  - West Virginia, 1931 (Box 37, Folder 97)
  - West Virginia, 1931 (Box 37, Folder 98)
  - West Virginia, 1931 (Box 37, Folder 99)
  - West Virginia, 1931 (Box 37, Folder 100)
  - A.H. Wright's Trips, 1929-34 (Box 37, Folder 101)
  - Texas, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 102)
  - Orchids in Texas, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 103)
  - Texas, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 104)
  - Helotes, Texas, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 105)
  - Texas, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 106)
  - Texas, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 107)
  - Texas, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 108)
  - Texas, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 109)
  - Texas, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 110)
  - Texas, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 111)
  - Colorado Desert, California, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 112)
  - A.H. Wright's Trips, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 113)
  - New Mexico and Nevada, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 114)
  - A.H. Wright's Trips, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 115)
  - Rolled group photograph of Cornell's class of 1904 (Box 37)
  - Cornell University Faculty, 1916 (Box 4)
  - Cornell University Faculty, 1916 (Box 4)
  - Frogs, 1932 (Box 4)
  - Cornell University Class of 1909 (Box 4)
  - Allen Family Photographs (Box 4)
  - "In quest of the new take the old with you" Christmas Card greeting (Box 4)
  - Book plate and negatives (Box 4)
  - Anna Allen as a young woman (Box 4)
  - Anna Allen as a middle aged woman (Box 4)
  - Cornell university Class of 1904 20th reunion, June, 1924 (Box 4)
  - Barbeque photographs, 1925 (Box 4)
  - Drawings of Pena Blanca, Arizona, 1934 (Box 4)
  - Drawings of Pena Blanca, Arizona (Box 4)
  - Jugatae group photo-A.H. Wright, 1924 (Box 4)
  - Group photographs from Cornell University-A.H. Wright (Box 4)
  - A.A. Wright's photographs (Box 4)
  - 1907-08 Group Photograph-A.H. Wright (Box 38)
  - 1908-09 Group Photograph-A.H. Wright (Box 38)
  - 1909-10-Group Photograph-A.H. Wright (Box 38)
  - A mounted photograph of the Brockport Normal School where A.H. Wright graduated in 1899. (Box 38)
  - Morrill Hall, Cornell University (Box 38)
  - The Alpha Delta Sorority at the Brockport Normal School (Box 38)
  - Map of the Okefinokee Swamp, 1945 (Box 38)
  - Pictures of snakes (Box 38)
  - Map of the United States (Box 38)
  - Pictures of snakes (Box 38)
  - Photographs of A.H. Wright, 1904-10 (Box 38)
  - Photographs of A.H. Wright (Box 38)
  - Photographs of A.H. and A.A. Wright (Box 38)
  - Photographs of A. H. Wright's trips, 1917-25 (Box 38)
  - Photographs of A. H. Wright (Box 38)
  - Photographs of A.H. Wright's family (Box 38)
  - Photographs of Allen Family (Box 43)
  - Photographs of Mr. & Mrs. Wright and Friends (Box 43)
  - Photographs of Anna A. Wright and Friends (Box 43)
  - Photographs of Moore Relatives (Box 43)
  - Photographs of Ancestors (Box 43)
  - Photographs of Ancestors (Box 43)
  - Photographs of A.H. and A.A. Wright (Box 43)
  - Photographs of A.H. and A.A. Wright (Box 43)
  - Photographs of Tramp (Box 43)
  - Photographs of Activities (Box 43)
  - Photographs of Activities (Box 43)
  - Photographs of Activities (Box 43)
  - Photograph of 222 Hudson St., Buffalo, NY (Box 43)
  - Photographs of C.C. Lin (Box 43)
  - Photographs of Family (Box 43)
  - Photographs, miscellaneous portraits (Box 43)
  - Photographs of Anna Allen, 1900 (Box 43)
  - Photographs of Anna Allen Wright (Box 43)
  - 1907-1908 Photo Album (Box 43)
  - Family Reunion Photo Album (Box 43)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 43)
  - Glass Picture of Anna Allen (Box 43)
  - Lantern slide, Texas (Box 43)
  - Photographs of 1925 Trip to Fort Davis, Texas (Box 43)
  - Scrapbook of Sullivan Expedition (Box 46)
  - 3 Scrapbooks (Box 62)
  - Subseries A: Negatives and Glass Plate Negatives
    - Texas, Arizona and California, 1925 (Box 39)
    - Miscellaneous negatives (Box 39)
    - Okefenokee Swamp pictures taken by F.H. Harper, 1921-22 (Box 40)
    - Iris Society photographs, 1927-28 (Box 40)
    - Monroe County, NY, 1904 (Box 41)
    - West Virginia, 1931 (Box 41)
    - A.H. and A.A. Wright (Box 43)
    - Activities (Box 43)
    - Anna Wright (Box 43)
    - 222 Hudson St., Buffalo, NY (Box 43)
    - New York and Pennsylvania (Box 44)
    - New York and Pennsylvania (Box 45)